dailyfinancegroup.com 2019-08-12

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains our views and practices concerning privacy, and how they may pertain to you as a user of our system.

"You" or "Your" means you, a participant in or as a user of the DAILY FINANCE GROUP programs.

"We" or "Our" or "Us" means DAILY FINANCE GROUP. "Our Website" also means DAILY FINANCE GROUP.

All information transmitted, printed or otherwise submitted to DAILY FINANCE GROUP through this Website remains your property; however, DAILY FINANCE GROUP will be free to use that information for any lawful purpose as detailed below.

This Website contains links to other websites. DAILY FINANCE GROUP is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

#### Section 1

Collected Information

DAILY FINANCE GROUP automatically collects and/or tracks the following information:

  1. Information knowingly provided by you through online forms, registration forms, surveys and/or other entries, such as your name, street address, e-mail address, telephone number (home, work and mobile), date of birth, Social Security Number, bank account information, information relating to monthly income, employment information, and other personal, financial or demographic information;
  2. Web page http headers (home server domain names, IP address, type of client computer, type of Web browser and operating system); 
  3. Information (user-specific or aggregate) concerning the pages our visitors access and referring URLs; and
  4. The e-mail addresses of visitors who communicate with this site and DAILY FINANCE GROUP via e-mail.

Submitting information to us is voluntary. However, if you would like to receive information on a loan-related product from one of our affiliated third-party loan providers (Affiliated Loan Providers), you must submit the required information, even if you do not actually enter into a formal application loan request with any Affiliated Loan Provider.

**Please note: We may also collect your personally identifiable information when you submit information at the Website but do not complete the full registration process.**

#### Section 2

Use of Data Collected

We use the information we collect to enhance your experience at our Website and to help us to offer content we determine may be of interest to you. We use your contact information to offer you promotional material from our partners. We may also use your personal, demographic, and profile data to improve our Website, conduct statistical analysis, and for marketing, promotional, editorial, or feedback purposes. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future e-mails or postal mailings of products and services.

#### Section 3

Disclosure of Data to Third Parties

By using this Website, you agree that you may be contacted in any manner contemplated in this section even if your phone number is included in a state, national, or federal do not call list. If you choose to provide personal information, it will be used for and/or shared with trusted third parties such as Affiliated Loan Providers and/or other financial service providers, credit bureaus, and for marketing products and services that you might find of interest. We reserve the right to share, rent, sell or otherwise disclose your information with/to third parties in accordance with applicable laws. These third-party businesses may include, but are not limited to: providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation; e-mail marketers; and telemarketers.

The information we collect may be added to our databases and used for future telemarketing via telephone calls, including telephone calls that may use an auto-dialer system, SMS text-messaging, instant messaging, e-mails or postal mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of orders and/or loans placed online.

We may also employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples may include sending direct mail and e-mail, removing duplicate information from customer lists, analyzing data, and providing marketing analysis. These agents have access to our users' personal information as needed to perform their functions for DAILY FINANCE GROUP, but we do not permit them to use our users' personal information for other purposes.

By agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you authorize us to use your information to obtain other information about you (for example, your Social Security Number) from third-parties when the information was incompletely or improperly filled out on our registration form. Third-parties include, but are not limited to, consumer reporting agencies, consumer credit bureaus and other outside parties, as permitted or required by applicable laws. Any and all Sensitive Information provided by you on this Site or on any third-parties Site, will be used to determine your eligibility for a loan or other products, offers or services, should you qualify. If you choose to provide information, such as your Social Security Number, we may use that information to determine your financial status. If you do not provide such information, we may also use other information that you provided for the purpose of verifying your eligibility for a loan or for any other programs, offer, or services. Upon qualification, your ultimate loan-specific financial information will be stored and utilized by your applicable lender in accordance with the terms of that lender's Privacy Policy.

DAILY FINANCE GROUP reserves the right to release current or past user information under the following conditions:

  * DAILY FINANCE GROUP believes that the service and/or Website is being or has been used in violation of the Website's Terms and Conditions or to commit unlawful acts,
  * If the information is subpoenaed,
  * If DAILY FINANCE GROUP or its affiliated web properties are sold or acquired, or
  * When DAILY FINANCE GROUP deems it necessary or appropriate. By agreeing to these conditions, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third party, when DAILY FINANCE GROUP, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third-parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time, and Federal Trade Commission enabling regulations.

By submitting your information at the Website, you agree to receive mobile marketing including, but not limited to, text-message based marketing from us and our third-party advertisers and marketers. Notwithstanding that your mobile telephone number may be listed on state and/or federal do-not-call registries, we retain the right to contact you via text message-based marketing, in accordance with applicable state and federal law. In addition, by registering and/or using the Website, you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or loan request for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR 310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (the "Rule") and the Telephone Consumer Protection Act (TCPA). Even though your telephone number may be listed at the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, we retain the right to contact you via telemarketing, in accordance with the Rule.

We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider. We will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator. You may opt-out and remove your SMS information by sending "X", "STOP", "END", "QUIT", or any other method to communicate to the sender that you no longer wish to receive messages, to the SMS text message you have received. If you remove your SMS information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you.

#### Section 4

Information Collection Processes

DAILY FINANCE GROUP may employ "cookies" to help customize your access to the Website. A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about you. Cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience at our Website. For instance, by setting a cookie on our Website, a user would not need to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our Website. Even in the case where a user rejects a cookie, they may still use our Website. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in what he/she can access in some areas on our Website, much like visitor-level access.

We may occasionally use cookies to anonymously track and target the interests of our users to further enhance the experience on our Website. We may also use cookies for advertising tracking purposes. To find out more about cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com.

In addition to cookies, our Website pages and/or e-mails may contain electronic images known as pixel tags (also known as clear gifs) to track the pages that visitors and/or users visit at the Website for purposes of formatting future campaigns and upgrading visitor information used in reporting statistics. Pixel tags from third parties may also be present on our Website to help determine the effectiveness of a joint promotional or advertising campaign.

#### Section 5

Use of Cookies

DAILY FINANCE GROUP and its affiliated web properties uses cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your online experience and to enable DAILY FINANCE GROUP to recognize you as a previous visitor to the DAILY FINANCE GROUP web properties. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Many sites do this whenever a user visits their website in order to track online traffic flows. Cookies record information about your online preferences. Users have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

DAILY FINANCE GROUP may also allow its partners and advertisers that are presenting advertisements on its web properties to set their cookies, or apply web beacons or similar technologies, to your computer. This information may be used to:

  1. remember the preferences and registration data that you give us;
  2. authenticate your Screen Name before you can access your Personal Information or Web Services Account for added security
  3. enable you to participate in certain online activities, such as making sure that each person only votes in an online poll once;
  4. personalize features of the DAILY FINANCE GROUP web pages, for example by providing you with customized content or advertisements based on the information you have submitted to us and your activity when using the DAILY FINANCE GROUP websites;
  5. help measure and research the effectiveness of the DAILY FINANCE GROUP web properties, including collecting statistics on your response to advertisements, e-mail and other communications you receive;
  6. provide security within shopping baskets or transactions.

DAILY FINANCE GROUP and its associated third parties may also use ad network providers to help present advertisements on DAILY FINANCE GROUP websites and other online properties. These ad network providers may use cookies, or web beacons or similar technologies on your computer to tailor content, advertisements to your preferences, help target, measure and track your visits and the effectiveness of advertisements and promotions, using data gathered over time and across their networks of Web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audience and to provide security within shopping baskets or transactions.

The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

You can adjust the settings on your browser to erase or block such technologies from your computer if you want to, but if you do so, you will not be able to use or access the DAILY FINANCE GROUP web pages provided.

#### Section 6

Electronic Disclosure

You are submitting your information to DAILY FINANCE GROUP via the Internet and agree to receive certain notifications, disclosures and/or documents electronically. This Electronic Disclosure and Consent Agreement applies to the information you are providing on this Site and any other communications we or any third parties discussed herein may provide to you. By submitting your information, you agree to receive all such notifications, disclosures and/or documents in electronic form or online in accordance with this document. You may withdraw your consent prior to submitting your information by exiting the website or by closing your browser. However, you will not be able to submit your information if you withdraw your consent by exiting the website or closing your browser. In addition, you cannot withdraw your consent after the submission of your information.

You consent to receive any notifications, disclosures and/or documents in electronic format.

All notifications, disclosures and/or documents that we or any third parties provide to you in electronic format will be provided either (i) via e-mail; (ii) by access to a secure customer service website which will be provided to you in an e-mail notice sent to you when the documents are available; (iii) by posting on this Site; or (iv) by posting on a website designated for that purpose.

All notifications, disclosures and/or documents provided in electronic or paper format from us or any third parties to you will be considered "in writing," and you should print a copy for your records by using the "print" button in your browser.

You are required to provide us with an accurate and complete e-mail address and other required information requested on this Site.

You may obtain any notifications, disclosures and/or documents in paper form without charge from us by printing them yourself from our website or the appropriate third-party website when available.

We and any third parties, reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to discontinue electronic provision of notifications and/or documents. You will be provided with notice of any such termination or change as required by law.

You agree and intend the federal Electronic Signatures in Global and National Commerce Act to apply to (i) this Consent to receive notifications, disclosures and/or documents in electronic form; (ii) the information you provide, and (iii) our and/or any third parties' ability to conduct business with you by electronic means.

To facilitate electronic commerce, to reduce the expense of records storage, and to obtain the benefits of faster access to records, you acknowledge and agree that all records may be stored electronically; and that neither we nor any third parties will retain and have no obligation to retain any original or electronic documents for any period of time beyond the regulatory requirements. This applies to all notifications, disclosures and/or documentation. You further acknowledge and understand that all original and electronic notification, disclosures and/or documentation will be routinely destroyed, but not before the period of time designated by regulatory requirements. Records may be stored electronically via imaging, scanning, filming or other technology used for the storage of documentation via internal processes or third-party processors that we or any third parties approve for these services. You agree that such storage shall be secure, and further agree that such records shall for all purposes be recognized and admissible in evidence or otherwise to prove the agreements, rights and obligations of the parties pursuant to any such records.

By completing and submitting your information, you (i) confirm your consent to receive notifications, disclosures and/or documents in electronic format; (ii) affirmatively demonstrate your ability to access the notifications, disclosures and/or documents in electronic form; (iii) confirm that you have provided a current e-mail address at which electronic notifications can be sent, disclosures and/or documents to you; iv) acknowledge that you have accessed the Consent; and (v) agree to the terms of this Consent.

#### Section 7

Your Opt-Out Rights

You may opt-out of receiving communications from us and or our third-party partners by not submitting your information. However, during registration and/or when you submit personally identifiable information to us at the Website, you have opted-in to request that we share your personal information (other than your Sensitive Information) with third parties to receive marketing communications. When contacted by any of these companies or third parties, you should notify them directly of your choices regarding their use and sharing of your information. As noted, we use personal information to provide promotional offers by e-mail to our Website users. DAILY FINANCE GROUP may prepare and use separate e-mail lists for different purposes. If e-mail recipients wish to end their e-mail subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each e-mail message to unsubscribe from the particular list. To opt-out from receiving any additional e-mail communications regarding the Website, please unsubscribe here.

In addition, if you subsequently sign up at one of our other websites for other product or service offerings, you will need to again address any information sharing preferences that you had previously established through this Website.

#### Section 8

Third Party Sites

In certain circumstances, DAILY FINANCE GROUP acts as a limited agent for the actual third-party lender or seller of the products and/or services available at or through the Website. In these circumstances:

a. | you will be redirected to the applicable third-party lender's or seller's website after you have completed entering your information;  
---|---  
b. | we will collect and send your personal information to the respective third-party lender or seller in connection with completing your loan request or purchase from the third-party lenders or seller, as applicable; and  
c. | your loan request or purchase will subject you to the third-party lender's or seller's privacy policy, as applicable.  
  
We do not endorse and are not responsible for the accuracy of the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of each of the third-party lenders or sellers that may advertise at the Website. The entities that advertise and/or place banner ads at the Website including, but not limited to, these third-party lenders and sellers, are independent third parties and are not affiliated with us.

#### Section 9

Your Rights to Your Personal Data

Upon receiving your request via postal mail or e-mail, we will provide you a summary of personal information retained by us. We will only send your personal records to your e-mail address or postal address that we have on file for you. To modify, correct, change, update or remove your personal record from our database, click here. 

#### Section 10

Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. For this reason, we never collect or maintain personal information at our website from those whom we know are under the age of 18 years old. In the event that information is inadvertently collected from children, it will not knowingly be used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside of our website. If we obtain actual knowledge that such information has been collected, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. The information and services provided by us or our affiliates, sponsors, and advertisers are not intended to be viewed by persons under 18 years old.

#### Section 11

Our Right to Contact You

We reserve the right to contact you regarding your account status and changes to subscriber agreements, Privacy Policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to you.

#### Section 12

Security

All information collected is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. Access to this information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. All of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personal information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all user information. Employees who do not adhere to our firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

#### Section 13

Our Right to Change

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. If changes are made, we will notify you of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy or by posting the changes online at our Website. All changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on our Website. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the DAILY FINANCE GROUP services, Websites or acceptance of our e-mails following the posting of changes to this Policy will mean that you accept any and all such changes and that you agree to continue receiving marketing from us and other third-party companies.

#### Section 14

Our Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, you can contact us:

Company Name: Verde Marketing LLC   
Address: 11184 Antioch, Suite 189, Overland Park, KS 66210 

#### Section 15

Information for ISPs

DAILY FINANCE GROUP understands consumers' concerns over the use of their personal information. We hope this information will relieve any concerns that your company may have regarding our e-mail policies.

DAILY FINANCE GROUP and its affiliated sites use only an "opt-in" or "opt out" method of obtaining customer information, and it is not our policy to send unsolicited e-mail. We obtain e-mail addresses and personal information from third parties that follow the same set of policies.

DAILY FINANCE GROUP e-mail messages sent include information about the origin of the e-mails and include instructions on how recipients can unsubscribe from receiving future e-mail message.

From time to time, DAILY FINANCE GROUP will enter into an arrangement with a third-party website to allow individuals to opt into our marketing program on those third-party websites. In each case, the third-party websites have represented and warranted to us, among other things, that the data was collected voluntarily from individuals on website registrations and co-registrations, that the sellers have a right, under any applicable privacy policies, to transfer the data to us, and that DAILY FINANCE GROUP has the right to send marketing offers to the individuals. We hope this information satisfies any questions or concerns you may have regarding the e-mail practices of DAILY FINANCE GROUP. If you have additional questions or wish to discuss this matter further, please visit our contact us page.
